<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kirsten Beyer on Sci-fi Books Club</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/tags/kirsten-beyer/</link><description>Recent content in Kirsten Beyer on Sci-fi Books Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 05:07:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scifibooks.club/tags/kirsten-beyer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Star Trek: Voyager: Full Circle book review</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/reviews/star-trek-voyager-full-circle-book-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 23:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/reviews/star-trek-voyager-full-circle-book-review/</guid><description>When Kirsten Beyer picked up the heavy gauntlet of the Voyager relaunch titles, she sure faced a challenge. Apart from tying up the loose ends from the preceding novels, she also had to: 1) Deal with &amp;ldquo;the Janeway thing&amp;rdquo; from Before Dishonor 2) Launch the Full Circle Fleet storyline 3) Work it all in with the aftermath of Star Trek: Destiny
Once more unto the Delta Quadrant, dear friends&amp;hellip;
Spoilers ahead</description></item><item><title>Star Trek: Voyager: Unworthy book review</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/reviews/star-trek-voyager-unworthy-book-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 22:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/reviews/star-trek-voyager-unworthy-book-review/</guid><description>&lt;p>There is something to be said for getting back to the status quo. Namely, putting the Voyager crew back into their original seats&amp;hellip; more or less. With &lt;em>Full Circle&lt;/em>, author Kirsten Beyer sent the U.S.S. Starship &lt;em>Voyager&lt;/em> hurtling back to the Delta Quadrant, thanks to some mean and lean slipstream technology. But the crew were still fractured, physically and emotionally — what will it take to bring Starfleet&amp;rsquo;s finest back to the adventure?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Star Trek: Voyager: Children of the Storm book review</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/reviews/star-trek-voyager-children-storm-book-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 05:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/reviews/star-trek-voyager-children-storm-book-review/</guid><description>Following up from two popular and successful Voyager novels, author Kirsten Beyer is back with her third post-Destiny Voyager instalment. Children Of The Storm takes place concurrently with the previous novel, Unworthy. Can Beyer score a hat-trick with book #3?
Spoilers ahead!
The titular “Children of the Storm” were first mentioned in David Mack’s Destiny trilogy. I don’t remember them, but apparently, they didn’t feature as much more than a throwaway line or two.</description></item></channel></rss>