<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Sci-fi Books Club</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Sci-fi Books Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:31:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scifibooks.club/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Interview with Una McCormack - Second Self</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/interview-with-una-mccormack/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/interview-with-una-mccormack/</guid><description>U﻿na McCormack was kind enough to take some time out of her busy writing schedule to answer some questions regarding her new Star Trek: Picard novel, Second Self.
I understand that Second Self was originally scheduled for publication earlier in the year, but was delayed due to paper shortages. Has it been a tough time lately as a writer? Do you find these sorts of delays frustrating? I think it’s tough for everyone at the moment, really.</description></item><item><title>A review of our reviews</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/a-review-of-our-reviews/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:02:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/a-review-of-our-reviews/</guid><description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been started to feel as though some of the book review scores given on Sci-Fi Books Club aren&amp;rsquo;t quite right. I&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed 30 books and never given a 5-star rating to any of them.
So what? It depends, I suppose, on what 5-stars means. When I first started writing reviews, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a baseline score system to work with. In essence, it was just a gut feeling. However, I don&amp;rsquo;t believe a 5-star score should only be given to the world&amp;rsquo;s most perfect book.</description></item><item><title>Star Trek Deep Space Nine S01E01 Emissary Mini-Review</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/star-trek-deep-space-nine-s01e01-emissary-mini-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 23:27:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/star-trek-deep-space-nine-s01e01-emissary-mini-review/</guid><description>Was I wrong about Deep Space Nine? Ask a Trekkie what their favourite Trek show is, and they&amp;rsquo;ll probably either say The Original Series or The Next Generation. Fair enough, those two are the biggest and most well-known iterations. But there will usually be one person lurking in the dark shadows of the room who will say, &amp;ldquo;Deep Space Nine is the best.&amp;rdquo;
Although Voyager and Enterprise certainly have their fans (I am a big Voyager fan), Deep Space Nine is often regarded as the unsung hero of Trek — a dark horse in the Trek canon.</description></item><item><title>Ebooks v Print Books - Which do you prefer?</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/ebooks-v-print-books-which-do-you-prefer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/ebooks-v-print-books-which-do-you-prefer/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a long time, I eschewed ebooks and e-ink reading devices such as the Kindle or the Kobo. I was a print purist. A physical book has that weight, smell, and special something that makes it special.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Or so I thought.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Wheel of Time Season One Mini Review</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/the-wheel-of-time-season-one-mini-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 02:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/the-wheel-of-time-season-one-mini-review/</guid><description>&lt;p>Many years ago, I tried to read the first &lt;em>The Wheel of Time&lt;/em> instalment. It had been recommended to me by a friend, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest here — I found &lt;em>The Eye of the World&lt;/em> to be a painfully dull read. It was slow, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t connect with any of the characters. I forced myself to the halfway point and then gave up.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>From here be spoilers!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Science fiction book reviews</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/science-fiction-book-reviews/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 03:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/science-fiction-book-reviews/</guid><description>At Sci-fi Books Club, we are all about reviewing science fiction books. We read the classics, new releases and everything in between. We love everything from the pulpy B-grade space opera classics — to the newer, more literary outings.
When we&amp;rsquo;re not busy reviewing books, we like to read other reviews too! There are a lot of novels out there, many more than we could possibly review even if we lived as long as Leto II.</description></item><item><title>Star Trek: Voyager complete series rewatch and review</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/star-trek-voyager-complete-series-rewatch-and-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 04:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/star-trek-voyager-complete-series-rewatch-and-review/</guid><description>&lt;p>Recently, I did a re-watch of &lt;em>Star Trek: Voyager&lt;/em>. From &lt;em>Caretaker&lt;/em> to &lt;em>Endgame&lt;/em>, it was quite a journey through the delta quadrant. Now, 20 years since the series finale, I have a few thoughts I&amp;rsquo;d like to share.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Star Trek Books Explainer</title><link>https://scifibooks.club/blog/trek-relaunch-litverse-post-nemesis-shared-continuity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 15:52:31 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://scifibooks.club/blog/trek-relaunch-litverse-post-nemesis-shared-continuity/</guid><description>&lt;p>Confused about all the Star Trek books? Confused by all the terms: Relaunch, litverse, post-Nemesis continuity? Not sure where and how to start with Treklit? This article is a simple explainer.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>